[There's a saying I really like.]
[If heaven]
[isn't my destination,]
[then hell]
[will be my paradise.]
[Welcome to my paradise,]
[and listen to my story.]
[Now,]
[it's just the beginning.]
Mr Zhou will be here shortly.
Coffee or tea?
No, thank you.
Li Sisi.
You like this painting very much,
and hang it in a prominent position.
The female fencer in the French fencing hall,
Lu Xu's fiancée,
Dark Fairy Tale's
Chief Designer.
What a coincidence!
The painter's name is Ziman,
It depicts her aspirations for the future
and her longing for marriage.
So,
it's such a beautiful ring.
Miss Jiang,
this is a company.
You should know that.
We just formally introduced
each other that day.
My name is Jiang Li.
graduated from ESMOD Paris,
winner of the French International Clothing Association Fashion Award,
a top luxury clothing designer,
and a student of Charles.
You haven't answered my question yet.
Life
is just a puppet show.
Thread to thread,
the living playing the dead.
The puppeteer, in a careless moment,
entangles two puppets together,
and hard to untangle.
Isn't that right?
Brother-in-law,
what exactly are you...
I just came by to check in today.
I just moved,
and there's still stuff to unpack at home.
Oh, by the way,
as your subordinate,
I hope to receive
your guidance in the future.
Come on, try it.
Yuxin,
you haven't changed a bit.
We haven't seen each other for years after graduation.
You didn't come see me when back.
Yuxin,
your dark circles
are almost reaching your mouth.
Don't mention it.
Since I opened this high-end wedding dress store after returning to China,
I haven't had a full night's sleep.
By the way,
your sister-in-law, Lu Qianqian,
is coming to try on a wedding dress later.
Oh.
I heard she's quite hard to deal with.
Don't underestimate me.
I've dealt with so many socialites.
Dealing with Lu Qianqian
is a piece of cake.
Wait.
Is your engagement to Lu Xu real?
Not a PR stunt?
Yeah.
You beat your principal in middle school,
got arrested for racing in high school,
barged into a bar drunk in college,
and made sexist comments online.
Don't tell me
you don't know any of this.
I know.
Then why...
Lil,
I don't know what you're thinking,
but
if the Lu family gives you any trouble,
come to me.
I may not be a rich second generation,
but I'm a first-generation entrepreneur.
Dealing with Lu Xu and Lu Qianqian
is a piece of cake for me.
Yes?
Boss.
The client has arrived,
but there's a problem.
Okay,
I'll be right there.
Yes?
You two better not meet.
I'll treat you to hot pot when I'm done.
Okay.
These two pearls have different luster.
And here,
it's so tight
that it's hard to breathe.
This outdated design from the last century,
do you call this haute couture?
Ms. Lu,
this mermaid dress features innovative cutting,
which can perfectly showcase...
Are you kidding me about my wedding?
Do you think
I'm just some small-time boss
or nouveau riche you usually deal with?
I'm sorry, Miss Lu.
I'll immediately replace the designer
and remake the dress for you.
This is your last chance.
If you still can't get it right,
this store
might as well close down.
[This wedding dress will be beautiful,]
[but you don't believe in fairy tales.]
[How could you possibly like]
[a wedding dress for a fairy tale princess?]
Jiang Li.
What are you doing here?
Senior,
bring the white sample dress with 3D pleats.
Oh, okay.
Go, go.
Take it off.
I'll remake it for you.
You want to make a wedding dress for me?
Trust me.
You'll like it.
This needs to be tightened half an inch.
You seem to know my body well.
Take a deep breath.
When I was studying in Paris,
I heard that when making clothes for prisoners on death row,
the collar should leave just enough room
for the rope on the gallows
to struggle.
You're provoking me.
Just kidding.
You actually took it seriously.
The wedding dress is a battle garment.
Beauty is a blade.
Your brother-in-law likes to touch here, right?
How did you get this scar?
I got scratched by a thorny vine when I was a child.
Later I found out
that the thorns are more interesting than the flowers.
A wedding dress is not just a candy coating for a princess,
but also a bait for hunting.
Look,
cracks can also be decorations.
You are really a
mysterious
and interesting weed,
which makes me want to get closer.
What kind of
variety are you?
What if I'm a man-eating plant?
You'll be in danger.
After all,
I work for Lu Xu.
It doesn't matter.
What matters is
if you can be mine.
Does your face
still hurt?
It's already swollen.
Mr. Zhou, you're so early.
Have you seen the painting?
It's over here.
A new work just arrived.
It's from Zimanteng.
Still that style,
a mix of sadness and determination.
But the woman in this painting
looks a bit familiar.
She looks a bit like Su Mu.
Still can't meet Zimanteng in person?
No way.
Money is not a problem.
Shi'an,
it's not about the money.
The artist herself doesn't want to show up.
I can't break the rules.
Wait.
Is the artist
male or female?
I can't tell you.
50,000 yuan.
Shi'an,
you're making it hard for me.
100,000 yuan.
Female.
After all these years,
this is all you can tell me?
Has the painting been delivered?
It's already in the study, sir.
Dad.
Dad,
the girl is playing the cello so well.
She's my aunt,
not my sister.
Li,
you play the violoncello so well.
Teach me
when you're free.
Honey,
you came back so late last night.
I haven't introduced her to you.
Jiang Li,
my guest for dinner.
You...
We...
Ah...
Jiang Li is Jiang Li,
Lu Xu is Lu Xu.
The problem between me and that jerk
doesn't affect Jiang Li and me
to become good sisters.
Baby,
let's eat later.
Lil,
what have you been busy with these days?
You couldn't even come shopping with me yesterday.
Come.
I just returned from abroad, so I'm quite busy.
Let me hold you while you eat.
Then let's hang out when you're free.